C.
Amy is talking with Millie about her problems in learning English.
Work in pairs and talk about the topic.
Use the conversation below as a model.
Millie, I'm really worried about my English.
Don't worry, Amy.
There are many ways to get better at English.
I think you can try listening to English as often as possible.
What should I listen to?
There are many online shows with people talking in English.
But remember, you don't have to understand every word.
Try to focus on the main idea of a talk or speech.
That's a good idea. What else?
How about reading English aloud every morning?
Try to pronounce each word correctly.
I'll have a try.
Thank you, Millie.